Guide to the Rosita Ella Hiscock papers, 1963-1965.
Hiscock, Rosita Ella papers,1963-1965.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Rosita Ella Hiscock papers, 1963-1965.
7454
Rosita Ella. Hiscock
.2 cubic ft.
Letters and cards.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Letters and cards received by Hiscock from Rodger C. Grubbs, 1963-1965, concerning a terminated love affair.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Letters and cards received by Hiscock from Rodger C. Grubbs, 1963-1965, concerning a terminated love affair.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Hiscock, Rosita Ella.; Grubbs, Rodger C.
Subjects:
Courtship.
Form and Genre Terms:
Love-letters.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting program: Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- Three Postcards, June 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Five Letters, Sept. 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Two Letters, Six Cards; Photograph of Grubbs, Oct. 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Two Letters, Two Cards, Nov. 1963-Dec. 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Three Letters; One Card; Photograph, Jan. 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Two Letters, One Card, One Note, Feb. 1964-Apr. 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Two Letters from Mrs. J.A. Grubbs, June 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Two Letters, Dec. 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Five Letters, Sample Marriage Liscense, July 1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Two Letters, One Card, Aug. 1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Two Letters, Sept. 1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Paraphernalia, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Pinx Box in which the Letters were stored, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 13)